I’m a mess mess mess mess mess mess mess
I’m a mess in distress but we’re still the best dressed
Fearless say yes we don’t dress to impress
괜찮단다 뭐를 해도
거짓말인 걸 난 알아
괜찮겠지 뭘 해도
착한 얼굴에 니 말 잘 들을 땐
괜찮지 않아 그런 건
내 룰은 나만 정할래 yeah
볼 거야 금지된 걸
Never hold back 더 자유롭게
Boom boom boom 내 심장이 뛰네
Get it like boom boom boom
Boom boom now
Boom boom boom 내 심장이 뛰네
Get it like boom boom boom
Push it I wish for what’s forbidden
I’m a mess mess mess mess mess mess mess
I’m a mess in distress but we’re still the best dressed
Fearless say yes we don’t dress to impress
웃어 웃어 더 인형이 되렴
덮어 덮어 다 감정 따윈 다
싫어 싫어 난 인형이 아냐
찡그린대도 그것도 나야
보지 말라 보고 파
날 둘러싼 이 금기들
그날의 이브처럼
Take it on the chain I know I like that
Boom boom boom 내 심장이 뛰네
Get it like boom boom boom
Boom boom now
Boom boom boom 내 심장이 뛰네
Get it like boom boom boom
Push it I wish for what’s forbidden
What you waiting for?
이게 타락이면 we fall fall fall
What you looking for
원한다면 now we fall we fall we fall
Boom boom boom 내 심장이 뛰네
Get it like boom boom boom
Boom boom now
Boom boom boom 내 심장이 뛰네
Get it like boom boom boom
Girl wanna have fun (girl)